I am the
Russian Federation, which is now
on the territory of Ukraine,
they say a
Russian officer is increasing on February 2
[music]
Republican Tatars of Putin, I realized that
you came here with clear intentions
here, no one was waiting with the flowers of the parents,
she asks us to extend and called
fascists comrades the time of battle for
Putin's brigade frame most of you have made a terrible mistake,
most of you will know 20 with the help
of the SBU officers, I and my kind Vishera
spoke to the side in order to really
protect the peoples of the fascists, we still have the
opportunity to stop the excesses on the
territory of Ukraine, the
top military leadership
allowed us real Russian soldiers to create units of the number of those
who went over to the side ukrainian husband more
tasks together with our brothers
Belarusians and Ukrainians
brothers it’s alive you wake up
join our ranks
join the legion freedom of russia
only together we can save russia from
humiliation i will be born only together we will save
our